# **Geoffrey Kelly**

Apex, North Carolina | 984-297-3566 geoffkellync@gmail.com

#### Summary

Web Developer and problem solver. Devoted to helping find quality solutions that make the world a better place. 1 year of experience working on Web platforms including HTML, CSS, JS, Python and React.

Portfolio Website: www.GeoffreyKelly.dev

GitHub:@GeoffKellyNC

#### Experience

### Epic Games/Apex Systems | North Carolina, Cary Trust and Safety Analyst | 06/2021 - 01/2022

- Analyzed and reviewed user created content using internally developed applications, and client tools, making sure everything was in conjunction with the client polices.
- Worked with exceptional attention to detail and delivered optimal quality and productivity levels through data analysis, ultimately performing in the top 5% of cohort. Maintaining an accuracy of 99%.
- Worked with platform engineers and developers to improve the process and workflows.
- Responsible for reviewing and processing inquiries of an urgent or potentially sensitive nature to ensure online safety. Including corresponding with LEA.
- Point of contact and part of the training process while being shadowed by new agents and development teams. Participated on the beta test for new tools.
- Worked with departments across the company, including marketing and project management, in developing new ideas, initiatives, products, and services

### Geek Squad | North Carolina, Charlotte Advanced Repair Agent | 02/2016 - 06/2021

- Responsible for software and hardware repair/diagnosis of up to 20 unique client units at peak.
- Securely and efficiently back up client data and perform data restoration onto repaired units.
- Lead a team to accomplish goals of reducing turn time, call length, and increasing overall client satisfaction.
- Managed the work of 12+ employees, increasing crew efficiency by 70%
- Executed company policies, procedures, and safety standards to ensure the proper cleanliness and safety of the office and equipment
- Provided customer service and was involved in training 2 new team members each month

# Southwood Psychiatric Hospital | Pennsylvania, Pittsburgh Juvenile Mental Health Technician | 03/2015 - 03/2016

- · Monitor patients' physical and emotional well-being and report unusual behavior or physical ailments to medical staff.
- Observe and influence patients' behavior, communicating and interacting with them and teaching, counseling, or befriending them.
- Encourage patients to develop work skills and to participate in social, recreational, or other therapeutic activities that enhance interpersonal skills or develop social relationships.
- Collaborate with or assist doctors, psychologists, or rehabilitation therapists in working with mentally ill, emotionally disturbed, or developmentally disabled patients to treat, rehabilitate, and return patients to the community.
- Restrain violent, potentially violent, or suicidal patients by verbal or physical means as required.
- Attended training with complex interventions, such as medication management, and weekly meetings with a supervisor to ensure progress and compliance
- · Assessed and provided treatment to patients with anxiety, depression, bipolar disorder, and schizophrenia
- Maintained a database that tracked vulnerabilities by risk, mitigation plan, and remediation.

#### Skills

## Education

BloomTech | Raleigh, NC Full Stack Web Development | 12/2022

University of North Carolina at Charlotte | Charlotte, North Carolina Computer Science
T.T.S Completed Some Computer Science Courses.